mamasgotittogether.com 2019-02-23

# Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy - Planning Inspired

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed  
by Planning Inspired. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use “Services”, or  
when you otherwise interact with us.  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify  
you by revising the “Last Updated” date at the top of this policy and, in some cases, we  
may provide you with additional notice (such as by adding a statement to our website or  
by sending you a notification). We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever  
you access the Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our  
information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

### Collection of Information

### Information You Provide to Us

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information  
when you create an account, participate in any interactive features of the Services,  
subscribe to a newsletter or email list, participate in an event, survey, contest or  
promotion, make a purchase, communicate with us via third-party social media sites,  
request customer support or otherwise communicate with us.  
The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, password,  
postal address, phone number, gender, date of birth, occupation, employer information,  
photo, payment information (such as your credit or debit card and billing address),  
preference or interest data, and any other information you choose to provide.  
If you provide an email address to invite a friend to participate in the Services, we will  
collect that email address and use it to send your friend such an invitation.

### Information We Collect Automatically

When you access or use our Services, we may automatically collect information about  
you, including:  
Log Information: We collect log information about your use of the Services, including your  
Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, web request, access times, pages viewed, web browser,  
links clicked and the page you visited before navigating to the Services.  
Mobile Device Information: We collect information about the mobile device you use to access  
our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique  
device identifiers, mobile network information and information about your use of our  
mobile applications.  
Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We and our service providers  
use various technologies to collect information, including cookies and web beacons.  
Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us  
improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services  
are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in  
our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and  
campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them,  
please see “Your Choices” below.

### Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information  
we collect through our Services. For example, if you create or log into your account  
through a third-party social media site, we will have access to certain information from  
that site, such as your name, account information and friends lists, in accordance with  
the authorization procedures determined by such social media site; we may also collect  
information about you when you post content to our pages/feeds on third-party social

### Use of Information

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:  
• Provide, maintain, improve and promote our products and services;  
• Provide and deliver the information, products and services you request, process  
transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and  
receipts;  
• Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and  
administrative messages;  
• Respond to your comments, questions and requests, and provide customer  
service;  
• Communicate with you about products, services, surveys, offers, promotions,  
rewards and events offered by Company and others, and provide news and  
information we think will be of interest to you;  
• Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;  
• Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or  
features that match user profiles or interests;  
• Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions, and process and deliver entries  
and rewards;  
• Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your  
needs and provide you with better service; and  
• Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.  
We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S.  
law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you  
consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other  
countries.

### Sharing of Information

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy  
Policy:  
• With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such  
information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf;  
• When you participate in the interactive areas of our Services, certain information  
you provide may be displayed to other users, such as your name, photo,  
comments and other information you choose to provide;  
• In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance  
with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process;  
• If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies,  
or to protect the rights, property and safety of Company or others;  
• In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company  
assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another  
company; and  
• With your consent or at your direction.

### Social Sharing Features

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the  
Facebook “Like” button), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other  
media, and vice versa. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with  
your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that  
provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope  
of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit  
the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

### Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others

We may allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to  
provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other  
technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites,  
including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked  
and conversion information. This information may be used by Company and others to,  
among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content,  
deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other  
websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about  
interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for  
behavioral advertising purposes by companies that participate in the Digital Advertising  
Alliance, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices.

### Security

Company takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss,  
theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.  
Your Choices  
Account Information  
You may review, correct or modify information maintained in your online account at  
any time by logging into your account and updating your profile information or by  
emailing us at sarah@planninginspired.com. If you wish to delete or deactivate your  
account, please email us at sarah@planninginspired.com, but note that some information  
you provide through the Services may continue to be accessible (e.g., comments you  
submit through the Services) and that we may continue to store information about you  
as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or  
archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually  
choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you  
choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability or functionality of  
our Services.

### Promotional Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by following the  
instructions in those communications or by sending an email to  
sarah@planninginspired.com. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional  
communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

### Push Notifications/Alerts

With your consent, we may send push notifications or alerts to your mobile device. You  
can deactivate these messages at any time by changing the notification settings on your  
mobile device.  
Contact Us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at  
sarah@planninginspired.com

Version: 1.0. Issue date: 05/09/18.

### COOKIE POLICY

We use cookies on our sites (www.planninginspired.com and the subdomains associated with  
www.planninginspired.com) (“our site”) for a number of purposes. They help us to provide you with a  
good experience when you browse our website, and also allow us to improve our site. By continuing to  
browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.  
A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your  
computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive.  
We use the following cookies:  
**Strictly necessary cookies.** These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website.  
They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a  
shopping cart or make use of the e-billing services.  
**Analytical/performance cookies.** They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and  
to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way  
our website works, for example, by ensuring that users find what they are looking for easily.  
**Functionality cookies.** These are used to recognize you when you return to our website. This enables  
us to personalize our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example,  
your choice of language or region).  
**Targeting cookies.** These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the  
links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed  
on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this  
purpose.  
You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use  
them below.

### First-party (IT Governance Ltd) cookies

This website will set some cookies that are essential for the website to operate correctly. These cookies,  
none of which capture personally identifiable information, are as follows:  
**Visitor ID** – this cookie is a numeric value that identifies unique visitors and provides coherence and  
consistency to a site visit;  
Page Number – this cookie identifies the page you are on;  
**Session ID** – this cookie identifies your website session;  
**Test** – this cookie checks whether or not your browser supports cookies;  
**Order** – this cookie ensures that your shopping basket works correctly.

### Third-party cookies

Our websites will set several types of third-party cookie, and we do not control the operation of any of  
them. The third-party cookies which may be set include:  
**Google Analytics** – we use Google Analytics to collect data about website usage. This data does not  
include personally identifiable information. You can view the Google Privacy Policy here:  
http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.  
**CommentLuv** – we use CommentLuv to give blog commenters the option to include a link to one of their  
recent blog posts with their comment. This data improves the users experience. You can opt out of using  
CommentLuv when posting your comments. For more information on this privacy policy contact the  
developer here: https://wordpress.org/plugins/commentluv/‹  
**Askimet** – we use Askimet to block spam comments. It’s a plug-in that blocks suspicious comments  
(including suspicious IP addresses) so that we don’t have to spend huge chunks of time deleting spam  
comments. You can view their terms of service right here: https://akismet.com/tos/

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of  
all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential  
cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.

### Affiliate Advertising

This website uses links, considered affiliate links, in which we earn a commission if a reader clicks through and makes a purchase. If you click through a link included on this site and make a purchase, we may earn a commission. We include a notice on each page that contains such links. To avoid this, simply open a new tab and go directly to the intended website or go through Google search to click. These sites use cookies, so if you click the links we may earn commissions through any purchase made for an extended time period, which varies depending on the company. You can turn off cookies in the same manner mentioned above. 

### Sponsored Content

Occasionally on this site, we publish sponsored content. With this content we have been compensated, either monetarily or through products, to speak about a product, brand, or service. We only recommend brands that we stand behind and do our best to post unbiased reviews. If we come across a product or service we don’t like, instead of recommending it to our readers, we simply don’t publish content on that product or service, that way we can continue to only publish unbiased content. You’ll find a notice on any content that is sponsored.
